哦，杰克就够了
Oh, just Jack's good enough, I reckon.
我不认识杰克
Don't know no Jack.
是吗，我想你应该增长见识
Well, maybe you ought to get acquainted.
他是这个国家最大的批发商
He's running the biggest wholesale business in the state.
你卖吗?
You selling?
是的
That's right.
我对非保税货没有兴趣
Ain't interested in no shiney.
我不卖非保税货物，我只卖保税货物
I ain't selling no shiney, I only deal in bonded goods.
哪种?所有的都做
- What kind? - All kinds.
我可以让你在三毛做一笔好交易
I can let you have a pretty good deal on some Three Feathers.
多少
How much?
好，那要看你出多少
Well, it depends.
你拿20个箱
You take 20 cases,
我会让它每箱卖到25
I'll let 'em go for $25 per.
那太贵了—还不算贵
- That's too much. - Ain't too much.
在合法的地方你不能这么便宜买到的
You can't get it that cheap where they sell it legal.
这里不合法吗
Ain't legal here.
你有好多理由做这笔交易
That's all the more reason you're getting a bargain.